本字幕由“听彧楼”发布
实力有限，如有错误，请指出及批评。
这是一场你死我活的游戏
我的蛇蝎美人你在哪里
我为你准备了一个惊喜
今晚 你输定了
我可没那么天真
嘿 就是你 请原谅我
Hey, over there, please forgive me
如果我来势太凶
If I'm coming on too strong
暗送秋波太落伍了 但你却大获全胜
Hate to stare but you're winning
我最爱的舞曲节奏已经响起
And they're playing my favorite song
放马过来 再靠近点
So come here a little closer
想和你说说悄悄话
Wanna whisper in your ear
搞清状况 问题是
Make it clear, little question
你对我到底有没有感觉
Wanna know just how you feel
如果我说我的心跳飚速
If I said my heart was beating loud
我们为何不愿离这拥挤的舞池
If we could escape the crowd somehow
要是我说我现在想要得到你
If I said I want your body now
你会欲擒故纵吗
Would you hold it against me?
因为你的感觉就是天堂
Cause you feel like paradise
今晚我需要放松一下
And I need a vacation tonight
所以当我说我渴望得到你时
If I said I want your body now
你会欲擒故纵吗
Would you hold it against me?
嘿 你会想我已经疯了
Hey, you might think that I'm crazy
但你知道我就是你的菜
But you know I'm just your type
我确实有点微醺
I might be a little hazy
但你不可否认
But you just cannot deny
我们磨出火花
There's a spark in between us
当我们在舞池狂欢时
When we're dancing on the floor
我想要更多想要识破
I want more, wanna see it
所以今晚我问你
So I'm asking you tonight
如果我说我的心跳飚速
If I said my heart was beating loud
我们为何不远离这拥挤的舞池
If we could escape the crowd somehow
要是我说我现在想要得到你
If I said I want your body now
你会欲擒故纵吗
Would you hold it against me?
因为你的感觉就是天堂
Cause you feel like paradise
今晚我需要放松一下
And I need a vacation tonight
所以当我说我渴望得到你时
So if I said I want your body now
你会欲擒故纵吗
Would you hold it against me?
当我说我想要得到你
if I said I want your body now
你会欲擒故纵么？
Would you hold it against me?
让我尝点甜头
Gimme something good
我现在就已迫不及待
Don't wanna wait, I want it now
大胆示爱吧
Pop it like a hood
让我知道你的本事
And show me how you work it out
如果我说我的心跳飚速
If I said my heart was beating loud
要是我说我现在就想得到你
If I said I want your body now
你会欲擒故纵吗
Would you hold it against me?
如果我说我的心跳飚速
If I said my heart was beating loud
我们为何不远离这拥挤的舞池
If we could escape the crowd somehow
要是我说我现在想要得到你
If I said I want your body now
你会欲擒故纵吗
Would you hold it against me?
因为你的感觉就是天堂
Cause you feel like paradise
今晚我需要放松一下
And I need a vacation tonight
要是我说我现在想要得到你
So if I said I want your body now
你会欲擒故纵吗
Would you hold it against me?
翻天覆地 翻天覆地 翻天覆地
Down and up And down and up And down and up and down
你的小把戏我早就识破了
I got all tricked out when I came up to this thing
看起来魅力爆表
Looking so fire hot, a twenty out of ten
我们在舞池中四目相交
I saw you watching me watching you on the floor
快来搭讪别再等待
Hitting me up like "What you waiting for?"
你可以大胆表露心声
It's alright to say you want it
潜入我满脑袋的坏点子里
Get inside my dirty mind
火热的视线今晚灼伤我一遍又一遍
Burns like ice the way I bring it again and again and again all night
刚一落拍满屋的性感
The beat just dropped and the room got sexy
你旁若无人紧盯着我
You're watching me like there's no one else around
对我饥渴就像想要糖的孩子
I know you want me like kids want candy
别移开视线跟我翻天覆地吧
So keep watching me go down
翻天覆地 翻天覆地 翻天覆地
Down and up And down and up And down and up and down
Down and up and down and up And down and up and down
围绕在你身旁的姑娘们也许讨厌我
All of dem girls you with they probably hating me
但是我知道他们只是在嫉妒
But I don't care because I know it's jealousy
他们巴不得我离开他们的视线
They see me on you like they think I'll give it up-up-up
但是老娘也不是省油的灯 不怕
But I ain't easy, just not afraid to rush
你可以大胆表露心声
It's alright to say you want it
潜入我满脑袋的坏点子里
Get inside my dirty mind
火热的视线今晚灼伤我
Burns like ice the way I bring it again
一遍又一遍
And again and again all night
刚一落拍满屋的性感
The beat just dropped and the room got sexy
你旁若无人紧盯着我
You're watching me like there's no one else around
对我饥渴就像想要糖的孩子
I know you want me like kids want candy
别移开视线跟我翻天覆地吧
So keep watching me go down
翻天覆地 翻天覆地 翻天覆地
And down and up And down and up and down Down and up
And down and up And down and up and down
翻天覆地 翻天覆地 翻天覆地
我能感觉我的蕾丝裙
I can almost feel my lace
震落当贝斯响起时
Slipping off cause of the bass
我能辨别出你因此按耐不住
I can tell that's what you're tripping on, tripping on
刚一落拍满屋的性感
The beat just dropped and the room got sexy
你旁若无人紧盯着我
You're watching me like there's no one else around
对我饥渴就像想要糖的孩子
I know you want me like kids want candy
别移开视线跟我翻天覆地吧
So keep watching me go down and up and down
刚一落拍满屋的性感
The beat just dropped and the room got sexy
你旁若无人紧盯着我
You're watching me like there's no one else around
对我饥渴就像想要糖的孩子
I know you want me like kids want candy
别移开视线跟我翻天覆地吧
So keep watching me go down and up and down
你好 多伦多
你们嗨不嗨？
我不能听到你们哈
1，2，3
One two three
不只我们两个
Not only you and me
来个80度大翻身
Got one eighty degrees
我摇摆不定 开始报数
And I'm caught in between Counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
彼得 保罗和玛丽
Peter, Paul & Mary
来个三人行
Getting down with 3P
人人都爱这游戏 开始报数
Everybody loves *** Counting
宝贝 挑个夜晚
Baby, pick a night
使出浑身解数
To come out and play
这就杠上了
If it's alright
你想说什么
What do you say?
越多越好
Merrier the more
就爱三重乐趣
Triple fun that way
在地板上缠绵
Twister on the floor
你想说什么
What do you say?
你要不要加入
Are you in
越轨是最新流行
Living in sin is the new thing (yeah)
你要不要加入
Are you in
开始报数
I am counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
不只我们两个
Not only you and me
来个80度大翻身
Got one eighty degrees
我摇摆不定 开始报数
And I'm caught in between counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
彼得 保罗和玛丽
Peter, Paul & Mary
来个三人行
Getting down with 3P
人人都爱这游戏
Everybody loves *** Counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
不只我们两个
Not only you and me
来个80度大翻身
Got one eighty degrees
我摇摆不定 开始报数
And I'm caught in between Counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
彼得 保罗和玛丽
Peter, Paul & Mary
来个三人行
Getting down with 3P
人人都爱这游戏
Everybody loves ***
三是重度魅力
Three is a charm
二是与众不同
Two is not the same
无伤大雅
I don't see the harm
因此 加入游戏么
So are you game?
让我们来组队
Let's make a team
轻唤我的名字
Make say my name
就爱极端方式
Loving the extreme
敢不敢玩一场
Now are you game?
你要不要加入
Are you in
越轨是最新流行
Living in sin is the new thing (yeah)
你要不要加入
Are you in
开始报数
I am counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
不只我们两个
Not only you and me
来个80度大翻身
Got one eighty degrees
我摇摆不定 开始报数
And I'm caught in between Counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
彼得 保罗和玛丽
Peter, Paul & Mary
来个三人行
Getting down with 3P
人人都爱这游戏 开始报数
Everybody loves *** Counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
不只我们两个
Not only you and me
来个80度大翻身
Got one eighty degrees
我摇摆不定 开始报数
And I'm caught in between Counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
彼得 保罗和玛丽
Peter, Paul & Mary
来个三人行
Getting down with 3P
人人都爱这游戏
Everybody loves ***
我们所作所为纯洁无罪
What we do is innocent
单纯追求乐趣
Just for fun and nothing meant
如果你不喜欢你的伴侣
If you don't like the company
也可以只有我跟你
Let's just do it you and me
那就只有你和我
You and me...
或三个
Or three....
或四个
Or four....
在地板上
On the floor!
One two three
1, 2, 3
不只我们两个
Not only you and me
来个80度大翻身
Got one eighty degrees
我摇摆不定
And I'm caught in between Counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
彼得 保罗和玛丽
Peter, Paul & Mary
来个三人行
Getting down with 3P
人人都爱这游戏
Everybody loves ***
One two three
1, 2, 3
不只我们两个
Not only you and me
来个80度大翻身
Got one eighty degrees
我摇摆不定 开始报数
And I'm caught in between Counting
One two three
1, 2, 3
彼得 保罗和玛丽
Peter, Paul & Mary
来个三人行
Getting down with 3P
人人都爱这游戏
Everybody loves ***
我从十七岁起就是个美国梦女郎
I’m Miss American Dream since I was 17
在荧幕上看到我也不要大惊小怪
Don’t matter if I step on the scene
或是偷溜去菲律宾度假
Or sneak away to the Phillipines
但杂志上依然有我翘臀的写真
They still got pictures of my derriere in the magazine
你想了解更多的我吗
You want a piece of me?
我是名利奢华的格调女王
I’m Mrs. Lifestyles of the rich and famous
我就是那个不知廉耻的布兰妮
I’m Mrs. Oh my God that Britney’s Shameless
我就是独家头条的新闻女王
I’m Mrs. Extra! Extra! this just in
我就是忽胖忽瘦的流行天后
I’m Mrs. she’s too big now she’s too thin
我是名利奢华的格调女王
I’m Mrs. Lifestyles of the rich and famous
我就是那个不知廉耻的布兰妮
I’m Mrs. Oh my God that Britney’s Shameless
我就是独家头条的新闻女王
I’m Mrs. Extra! Extra! this just in
我就是忽胖忽瘦的流行天后
I’m Mrs. she’s too big now she’s too thin
你想了解更多的我吗
You want a piece of me
别人可以夺走你的一切
但却夺不走你真实的自我
问题是
你能把持住自己么？
他们说我疯了
我们又见面了 我的蛇蝎美人
你用这些魅惑的微笑引诱着我
让我意识不到我自己正身处危险之中
上一次 一群小丑害我把你跟丢了
而现在 你在莫斯科
巴黎
摩洛哥
你在哪里 我的蛇蝎美人
下一个跪倒在你石榴裙下的男子是谁
我本来的梦想是统治整个世界
可是你改变了我的梦想
你毁了我的梦想
我找到你了
我警告过你 可是你不听
所以现在是时候了
秀出你的真本事吧
因为今晚我们要决一死战
这场战斗是如此特别
你肯定已经感觉到肾上腺素在体内流动了吧
因为我也有同样的感觉
我感觉到了
我准备好了
你呢？
（猥琐）@_@
重低音 ~ 重低音
Big fat bass, the big fat bass
我来当高音 宝贝 你来当我的贝斯
I can be the treble baby, you can be the bass
你来当我的贝斯 ~ 你来当我的贝斯
You can be the bass, you can be the bass
我来当高音 宝贝 你来当我的贝斯
I can be the treble baby, you can be the bass
你来当我的贝斯 ~ 你来当我的贝斯
You can be the bass, you can be the bass
嘿 你看见我在舞池热舞
Hey  You see me down on the floor
我想你让我更嗨
I want you to take me higher
直到我受不了为止
Till I can't take it no more
节奏渐强贝斯加重 ~ 节奏渐强贝斯加重
It's getting bigger, the bass is getting bigger
我来当高音 宝贝 你来当我的贝斯
I can be your treble baby, you can be my bass
你来当我的贝斯 ~ 你来当我的贝斯
You can be my bass, you can be my bass
我来当高音 宝贝 你来当我的贝斯
I can be your treble baby, you can be the bass
你来当我的贝斯 ~ 你来当我的贝斯
You can be my bass, you can be my bass
节奏渐强贝斯加重 ~ 节奏渐强贝斯加重
It's getting bigger, the bass is getting bigger
节奏越来越重
It's getting bigger bigger bigger
贝斯节奏开始低了
The bass is getting low
嘿 你看见我彻夜徘徊
Hey  You see me out in the night
准备彻夜劲舞
Wanna go out dancing
所以我倍感愉悦
So I can feel alright
节奏渐强贝斯加重节奏渐强贝斯加重
It's gettin bigger, the bass is gettin bigger
我来当高音 宝贝 你来当我的贝斯
I can be your treble baby, you can be my bass
你来当我的贝斯 ~ 你来当我的贝斯
You can be my bass, you can be my bass
我来当高音 宝贝 你来当我的贝斯
I can be your treble baby, you can be my bass
你来当我的贝斯 ~ 你来当我的贝斯
You can be my bass, you can be my bass
Yo, yo
准备下个拍点全场热舞
Y'all better get ready for the kick drum
下个拍点 ~ 下个拍点
For the kick drum, for the kick drum
准备下个拍点全场热舞
Y'all better get ready for the kick drum
下个拍点 ~ 下个拍点
For the kick drum, for the kick drum
拍点来了 来点声音炒热舞场
Yo it's the kick drum, come and get some
让身体产生共鸣
Of the sound that's rocking your system
像毒药一样越舞越上瘾
When it pounds, it cause an addiction
却没有解药
Y'all addicts better have a prescription
我和布布全场热舞
Me and Brit got the whole club tripping
他们坐等聆听
They sit and wait and listen
下个拍点 ~ 下个拍点
For the kick drum, for the kick drum
超大大大~贝斯
For the big big fat fat bass
摇摆舞动全出击
Rocking all in your face
舞动节拍嗨翻全场
Vibrate, shake up the place
现在就让我们狂欢
Right now let's get crazy
一起来吧
Here we go
全场陷入疯狂
Everybody in the place get frantic
节奏进入高潮
This beat right here's gigantic
Yo
节奏进入高潮 ~ 节奏进入高潮
It's getting bigger, the bass is getting bigger
我来当高音 宝贝 你来当我的贝斯
I can be your treble baby, you can be my bass
你来当我的贝斯 ~ 你来当我的贝斯
You can be my bass, you can be my bass
我来当高音 宝贝 你来当我的贝斯
I can be your treble baby, you can be my bass
你来当我的贝斯 ~ 你来当我的贝斯
You can be my bass, you can be my bass
我来当高音 宝贝 你来当我的贝斯
I can be your treble baby, you can be the bass
你来当我的贝斯 ~ 你来当我的贝斯
You can be my bass, you can be my bass
你好 多伦多
来听我的《飙舞》
激情燃烧 我们还要再喝一轮
Burn it all down, gonna buy another round
喇叭声中点亮活力
Gonna light up in the sound of the speaker
性感长袜 龙蛇一杯接着一杯
Knee socks, drink tequila on the rocks
直到让你的身体跟喇叭一样舞动
Till you make your body pops to the speaker
激情燃烧 我们还要再喝一轮
Burn it all down, gonna buy another round
喇叭声中点亮活力
Gonna light up in the sound of the speaker
秀出你性感的长袜 龙蛇一杯接杯
Show your knee socks, drink tequila on the rocks
直到让你的身体跟喇叭一样舞动
Till you make your body pops to the speaker
我要找到我的完美定位
(I wanna go) rock downtown where my posse's at
因为我是九命猫妖
(Because I got) nine lives like a kitty cat
你想要舞动 这便是我的飙舞
(You wanna roll, that's how I roll)
当我听到重低音时就身体不听使唤
(I wanna go) ring ring when I hear that bass
你要是想试试看 那我就激进迷情
(I'm gonna do) my thing if you want a taste
你最好知道 这便是我的飙舞
(You better know that's how I roll)
Bum bum bum ba da dee dum bum bum
舞到地震 身体天旋地转
Feel the earthquake, gonna make your body shake
直到你对着喇叭绕地球一圈
Till the circuits start to break in the speaker
飘飘欲仙 直升机直冲云霄
Can we get fly, helicopter in the sky
因为我们对着喇叭 越来越嗨
Cause we turn it up high in the speaker
你想成为我的人
If you know what it takes to be my man
我们便能水乳交融
We can go make love together
来当我今夜的情人
You can be my thug tonight
我们便能彻夜狂欢
We can tear it up tonight
我要找到属于我的完美定位
(I wanna go) downtown where my posse's at
因为我是九命猫妖
(Because I got) nine lives like a kitty cat
你想要舞动 这便是我的飙舞
(You wanna roll, that's how I roll)
当我听到重低音时就身体不听使唤
(I wanna go) ring ring when I hear that bass
你要是想试试看 那我就激进迷情
(I'm gonna do) my thing if you want a taste
你最好知道 这便是我的飙舞
(You better know that's how I roll)
当我听到重低音时就身体不听使唤
(I wanna go) ring ring when I hear that bass
你要是想试试看 那我就激进迷情
(I'm gonna do) my thing if you want a taste
你最好知道 这便是我的飙舞
(You better know that's how I roll)
Bum bum bum ba da dee dum bum bum
就是这样 这样 喔~
Shimmy shimmy oh, shimmy oh shimmy eh
他们的满足与否都随我们掌控
We can give 'em what they want or we could take it away
今晚尽力爱
Try love tonight
我们便能彻夜狂欢
We can tear it up tonight
我要找到属于我的完美定位
(I wanna go) downtown where my posse's at
因为我是九命猫妖
(Because I got) nine lives like a kitty cat
你想要舞动 这便是我的飙舞
(You wanna roll, that's how I roll)
当我听到重低音时就身体不听使唤
(I wanna go) ring ring when I hear that bass
你要是想试试看 那我就激进迷情
(I'm gonna do) my thing if you want a taste
你最好知道 这便是我的飙舞
(You better know that's how I roll)
Bum bum bum ba da dee dum bum bum
谢谢 多伦多
现在要找一位志愿者来帮我完成下个演出
我看看有人愿意么  哗！
好多人呀
小甜甜 我来帮你挑一个吧
当然好
那个地方的怎么样
那个地方有点远了
是蛮远的
蓝色衣服的怎么样
蓝色T恤的小伙子行不行
我觉得他有女友在 o
那个是他女友啊
好甜蜜呀 O_o
不好意思呀
选围栏附近的吧
叫什么名字呀
艾伦  (=^0^=)
给艾伦一些掌声哈
好的 艾伦
你只需坐下放松就好
表演开始了
（小燕子姿势）
法式亮甲配上红唇 火辣的不好惹
French fingertips, Red lips Bitch is dangerous
棉花糖味儿香吻 想快点开始我的糖果大战
Cotton candy kiss can't wait for my sugar rush
再也忍不住了
Can't take it no more
今晚我要尽情玩乐
I got to have more tonight
欲望挡不住
This feelings so strong
今晚我要给你好看
I'm putting you on tonight
这就对了 好戏开始了
Alright! Let's Go!
宝贝快坐好 因为我要趁火打劫
Baby take a seat as your weakness is my show
你让我心花怒放
Your one and only pleasure
沾满浑身蕾丝和皮革
All decked in lace and leather
快对端庄典雅的我下手吧
Fantasy, Courtesy, Me Baby let's go!
看着我芳心荡漾
Watch me apply the pressure
沾满浑身蕾丝和皮革
All decked in lace and leather
他是回不来了。嘿嘿
喔 甜心 你今晚见到艾米没
Oh baby, baby, have you seen Amy tonight
她是在洗手间化妆
Is she in the bathroom
还是在外面抽烟
is she smoking up outside
喔 甜心 她是不是吃了一片酸橙
Oh, baby, baby, does she take a piece of lime
我能出钱给她买点喝的
For the drink that I’m-a buy her
你晓得她打扮是什么样吗
do you know just what she likes
喔 请告诉我下你见到她没有 因为我好..喔
Oh, oh, tell me have you seen her, cause I’m so, oh...
我实在无法忘记她
I can’t get her off of my brain
我就想去下她要参加的派对
I just wanna go to the party she gone go
谁都别想送我回家
Can’t somebody take me home
哈哈 呵 哈哈 呵
Ha ha hee hee ha ha ho
爱上我 记恨我 口口声声说想拥有我
Love me, hate me, say what you want about me
但所有的男生女生都在急切渴望
But all of the boys and all of the girls are begging to
倘若你找到艾米
If U seek Amy
爱上我 记恨我 但你无法瞧见我所目睹的
Love me, hate me, but can’t you see what I see
所有的男孩女孩们都在热切期盼
All of the boys and all of the girls are begging to
倘若你找到艾米
If U seek Amy
艾米说了要和我碰头
Amy told me that she’s gonna meet me up
我压根不晓得该在哪时哪刻 他们都在酒吧里蠢蠢欲动
I don’t know where or when and now they’re closing up the club
在她懂我前我曾见过她几次面
I’ve seen her once or twice before she knows my face
但要在拥挤的人群中认出她简直难上加难
But it’s hard to see with all the people standing in the way
喔 请告诉我下你见到她没 因为我好
Oh!Tell me, have you seen her Cause I'm so
喔！我实在无法忘记她
oh!I can't get her off of my brain
我就想去下她要参加的派对
I just wanna go to the party she gone go
谁都别想送我回家
Can somebody take me home
哈哈 呵 哈哈 呵
Ha ha he he ha ha ho
爱上我 记恨我 口口声声说想拥有我
Love me, hate me say what you want about me
但所有男孩女孩们都在急切渴望
But all of the boys and all of the girls
倘若你找到艾米
Are begging to if U seek Amy
爱上我 记恨我 但你无法瞧见我所目睹的
Love me, hate me But can't you see what I see
所有的男孩女孩们都在热切期盼
All of the boys and all of the girls
倘若你找到艾米
Are begging to if U seek Amy
喔 口口声声说想拥有我
Oh…Say what you want about me
喔 但却无法瞧见我所目睹的
Oh…But can't you see what I see
口口声声说要拥有我
Say what you want about me
请你告诉我如果你见到她了
tell me if you see her
因为我为她守候一生
Cause I've been waiting here forever
喔 甜心 倘若你今晚见到艾米
Oh baby baby If U seek Amy tonight
喔 甜心 我会为你奋不顾身
Oh baby baby We'll do whatever you like
喔 宝贝 宝贝 宝贝
Oh baby baby baby
爱上我 记恨我 口口声声说想拥有我
Love me, hate me say what you want about me
但所有男孩女孩们都在热切渴望
But all of the boys and all of the girls
倘若你找到艾米
Are begging to if U seek Amy
爱上我 记恨我 但你无法瞧见我所目睹的
Love me, hate me But can't you see what I see
所有男孩女孩们都在热切期盼
All of the boys and all of the girls
倘若你找到艾米
Are begging to if U seek Amy
喔 口口声声说想拥有我
Oh… Say what you want about me
喔 但却无法瞧见我所目睹的
Oh… But can't you see what I see
喔 口口声声说想拥有我
Oh… Say what you want about me
喔 但却无法瞧见我所目睹的
Oh… But can't you see what I see
爱上我 记恨我 但你无法瞧见我所目睹的
Love me, hate me But can't you see what I see
所有男孩女孩们都在热切期盼
All of the boys and all of the girls
着
are
倘若你找到艾米
begging to if U seek Amy
女人到底是怎么了
早在远古的时候
每个君王就都被她们迷得神魂颠倒
蛇蝎美人
加速了世界
进步的步伐
埃及艳后
有着绝世美貌 极度诱惑
多少男人为其鬼迷心窍不惜一切代价想得到她
印度艳后
用妙曼的舞姿把男人们引入闺房
再诱使他们说出自己的秘密
法国艳后
即使出身贫寒
也会在皇帝面前狐假虎威
强迫臣民来认出她
而现在 是你
和那些蛇蝎美人的传说一样
就算你有着和他们相同的手段
也还是脱离不了最终要灭亡的命运
我为你准备了一个惊喜
在我和你说话的时候 应经有一支美男军队整装待发
就算你不在我手里死去
我敢保证
他们之中肯定有一个可以干掉你
今晚 你输定额
就是你
I see you
我想与你共舞
And I just wanna dance with you
每当灯光渐熄
Everytime they turn the lights down
我愿为你共赴良宵
Just wanna go that extra mile for you
你感受到我爱的指示
Public display of affection
就好像你我共处一室
Feels like no one else in the room (the room)
我们可以独自享乐
We can get down like theres no one around
我们尽情摇摆 尽情摇摆
We keep on rocking , we keep on rocking
镜头捕捉到的尽是煽情舞动
Cameras are flashing while we're dirty dancing
他们持续监看 持续监看
They keep watching, keep watching
好像大家都在暗示
Feels like the crowd was saying
给我更多^_^
Gimme Gimme more Gimme more
给我更多^_^|||
给我更多^_^"
Gimme Gimme more Gimme more
给我更多→_→
给我更多@_@|||||
Gimme Gimme more Gimme more
给我更多(⊙_⊙)
即使处境艰困
Centre of attention
依然是中心焦点
even when you’re up against the wall
你让我陷入疯狂
You got me in a crazy position
如果你冲着我来
If you’re on a mission
我会给你选择的空间
You got my permission ooohhh
我只要你给我更多
I just want more
好像大家都在暗示
Feels like the crowd was saying
给我更多( # ^.^ # )
Gimmie gimmie more,gimmie more
给我更多p( ^ O ^ )q
给我更多\ ( O
给我更多＼( ^▽^ )／
Gimmie gimmie more,gimmie more
给我更多( ' – ' )
给我更多(~^O^~)
Gimmie more
给我更多( @o@ )||||
(Gimmie gimmie more,gimmie more)
给我更多( +_+ )
Gimmie gimmie more,gimmie more
钻石钻石闪闪惹人爱
Diamond, diamond Shining, shining
宝贝 你如此秀色可餐
Ooh boy You so fine
肯定是我此生看过最耀眼的宝贝
Gotta be the finest thing That I seen in my life
不惜一切代价 我也要目睹你的风采
I will pay whatever Just to get a better view
你的身材如此完美 我迷得无药可救
And yeah, your body looks so sick I think I caught the flu
看到你 看到你
Look at you Look at you
今夜当我的情人我的甜心吧
Be my sweetie Be my honey tonight
看到你 看到你
Look at you Look at you
今夜当我的情人我的甜心吧
Be my sweetie Be my honey tonight
你如此美丽（让我窒息）
Cause, you're beautiful (Drop dead)
美丽（让我窒息）
Beautiful (Drop dead)
Beautiful (Drop-drop dead)
美丽（让我窒息）
Beautiful (Drop dead)
你实在太美好了
You're some kind of fine
帅哥 你知道你很美丽
Boy, you know You're beautiful
想必你也曾受到夸赞
I know you heard it before
帅哥 你知道你颠覆美学
Boy, you know You broke the mold
别人都望尘莫及
Nobody even comes close
你实在太美好了
You're some kind of fine
You must be b-i-g
因为你让我着迷
Because, you got me hypnotized
谁都说美丽包装下是蛇蝎心肠
Whoever said that beauty's on the inside is a liar
我现在可正注视着你哦 你让少妇都哭泣
Cause, what I'm looking at right now Would make a big girl cry
系上安全带这可是一次颠簸的旅程
So fasten up your seatbelt It's gone be a bumpy ride
看到你 看到你
Look at you Look at you
今夜当我的情人我的甜心吧
Be my sweetie Be my honey tonight
看到你 看到你
Look at you Look at you
今夜当我的情人我的甜心吧
Be my sweetie Be my honey tonight
你如此美丽（让我窒息）
Cause, you're beautiful (Drop dead)
美丽（让我窒息）
Beautiful (Drop dead)
Beautiful (Drop-drop dead)
美丽（让我窒息）
Beautiful (Drop dead)
你实在太美好了
You're some kind of fine
帅哥 你知道你很美丽
Boy, you know You're beautiful
想必你也曾受到夸赞
I know you heard it before
帅哥 你知道你颠覆美学
Boy, you know You broke the mold
别人都望尘莫及
Nobody even comes close
你实在太美好了
You're some kind of fine
我想我爱上你了
I think I like you
帅哥帅哥 看看你 让人情不自禁想靠近你
Boy, boy Look at you I wanna get, get, get next to you
让我热起来吧 我不会让你太累
Got me kinda hot But, I ain't sweating you
蒸了我 就像盘菜一样
Steam me like like a pot full of vegetables
帅哥帅哥看看我 你想占我便宜没那么容易
Boy, boy Look at me I know you wanna touch But it ain't for free
我不要你的钱 只想要你的情
I don't need your money I just want your D
挺着你的翘臀过来吧
Boy, come over here with your sexy ass
你如此美丽（让我窒息）
Cause, you're beautiful (Drop dead)
美丽（让我窒息）
Beautiful (Drop dead)
Beautiful (Drop-drop dead)
美丽（让我窒息）
Beautiful (Drop dead)
你实在太美好了
You're some kind of fine
帅哥 你知道你很美丽
Boy, you know You're beautiful
想必你也曾受到夸赞
I know you heard it before
帅哥 你知道你颠覆美学
Boy, you know You broke the mold
别人都望尘莫及
Nobody even comes close
你实在太美好了
You're some kind of fine
[Don't Let Me Be The Last To Know]
朋友说你对我很着迷
My friends say you're so into me
甚至对我痴情满满
And that you need me desperately
你说我们是天生一对
They say you say we're so complete
但我想要亲口听你说
But I need to hear it straight from you
倘若你想让我相信你
If you want me to believe it's true
等待已经让我饱受折磨
I've been waiting for so long it hurts
我真的好想听你说
I wanna hear you say the words, please
千万不要让我最后一个人知道
Don't, don't let me be the last to know
别退缩 让心声袒露
Don't hold back, just let it go
我需要听你说出来
I need to hear you say
你想我留在你身边
You need me all the way
喔 倘若你真的爱我
Oh, if you love me so
千万别让我最后一个人知道
Don't let me be the last to know
说出来 宝贝
Come om baby, oh yeah
我需要听你说出来
I need to hear you say
你想我留在你身边
You love me all the way
我已不愿漫长地等待
And I don't wanna wait another day
我好想跟你心心相印
I wanna feel the way you feel
喔 说出来
Oh, come on
不要  让我成为你的唯一
Don't, just let me be the one
别退缩 让心声袒露
Don't hold back, just let it go
我需要听你说出来
I need to hear you say
你想我留在你身边
You need me all the way
所以说宝贝 倘若你爱我
So…baby, if you love me
千万别让我最后一个人知道
Don't let me be the last to know
[Boys]
不知为何
For whatever reason
我觉得我这辈子就在等你出现
I feel like I′ve been wanting you all my life
但你不了解
But you don′t understand
我好高兴我们在一起相遇在同一个时刻
I′m so glad we′re at the same place at the same time
但现在都结束了
Its over now
我看见你跳舞
I spotted you dancing
你让所有的女孩目不转睛
You made all the girls stare
那对双唇那对褐眼
Those lips and your brown eyes
还有那性感的头发
And the sexy hair
我应该摆动身体
I shake/should shake my thing
让全世界都想拥有你
I make the world want you
告诉兄弟们你待会就回来
Tell your boys you′ll be back
我要看看你的能耐
I wanna see what you can do
你跟我走会怎么样
What would it take for you to just leave with me
不是我太自信
Not trying to sound conceited
但我跟你注定要在一起
But me and you were meant to be
你是个性感的帅哥 我是个好姑娘
You′re a sexy guy I′m a nice girl
让我们把这个舞池变成我们狂野的小世界
Let’s turn this dance floor into our own little nasty world
男孩 有时女孩就是需要男孩
Boys Sometimes a girl just needs one
男孩 女孩需要你去爱她宠她
Boys to love her and to hold
男孩 当女孩身边有一个
Boys when a girl is with one
男孩 那她就掌控大权了
Boys Then she′s in control
带你的男孩离开舞池
Pull your boy off the dance floor
跟她交头接耳
Screamin in his ear
一定是在说关于我的事儿
Must of said something but me
因为他正往我这看
Cuz he′s looking over here
你用性感的姿态看着我
You're looking at me with a sexy attitude
但你跟兄弟的样子
But the way that boys moves it
让我心情超好
It puts me in the mood
你跟我走会怎么样
What would it take for you to just leave with me
不是我太自信
Not trying to sound conceited
但我跟你注定要在一起
But me and you were meant to be
你是个性感的帅哥 我是个好姑娘
You′re a sexy guy I′m a nice girl
让我们把这舞池变成我们狂野的小世界
Let’s turn this dance floor into our own little nasty world
女孩 只想跟你在一起
Girls,I can't speak for no one
女孩 我想无时无刻跟你在一起
Girls,when I need them all the time
女孩 我想更懂你
Girls,I don't know about your girl
女孩 我好想拥有你
Girls,but I know she ain't talked to mine
男孩 有时女孩就是需要男孩
Boys Sometimes a girl just needs one
男孩 女孩需要你去爱她宠她
Boys to love her and to hold
男孩 当女孩身边有一个
Boys when a girl is with one
男孩 那她就掌控大权了
Boys Then she′s in control
赶快行动
Like that,Here we go~
狂欢一下
Get nasty
这是一场你死我活的游戏
她可真能逃啊 是不是
只有这样的猎物才有追捕的价值
不过这回 你耍什么花招都没有用
[...Baby One More Time]
喔 宝贝宝贝
Oh baby,baby
我怎么会知道
How was I supposed two know
有些事情不太对劲
That something wasn't right here
喔 宝贝宝贝
Oh,baby baby
我本不该让你离开我
I shouldn't have let U go
现在你已杳无音信
And now U're out of sight yeah
告诉我你想怎样
Show me how U want it two be
告诉我宝贝
Tell me baby
因为我需要现在知道
Cause I need two know now
哦 因为
Oh,because
寂寞孤独我承受不住
My loneliness is killing me
我得承认
(And I)I must confess
我仍然相信
I still believe
仍然相信
(Still believe)
当不和你在一起时我迷失了方向
When I'm not with U I lose my mind
给我个爱的信号
Give me a sign
宝贝再次拥抱我吧
Hit me baby one more time
我必须承认
I must confess
寂寞孤独我承受不住
That my loneliness is killing me now
我仍然相信你会回来
Don't U know I still believe that U will be here
给我个爱的信号
Give me a sign
宝贝再次拥抱我吧
Hit me baby one more time
[S&M]
肆情放纵一晚
Just one night full of sin
享受肌肤上的痛感
Feel the pain on your skin
喜欢来硬的 冲上高潮
Tough,I don't scream mercy
换你来作弄我
It's your turn to hurt me
要是我不乖就捆起来
If I'm bad tie me down
堵住我的嘴 别让我说话
Shut me up gag and bound me
因为痛起来感觉很过瘾
Cuz the pain is my pleasure
没比这更爽的了
Nothing comes better
因为我坏透了 但这也是我的拿手好戏
Cuz I may be bad but I'm perfectly good at it
腥味弥漫 不介意这闻起来太棒了
Sex in the air I don't care I love the smell of it
粗棍和石头会弄疼我
Sticks and stones may break my bones
可铁链和皮鞭会上瘾
But chains and whips excite me
因为我坏透了 但这也是我的拿手好戏
Cuz I may be bad but I'm perfectly good at it
腥味弥漫 不介意这闻起来太棒了
Sex in the air I don't care I love the smell of it
粗棍和石头会弄疼我
Sticks and stones may break my bones
可铁链和皮鞭会上瘾
But chains and whips excite me
啦啦啦啦 放马过来
Nananana come on come on
我喜欢喜欢 放马过来
I like it like it come on come on
这是禁忌游戏
SSSS&MMMM
[Trouble For Me]
来赌一把配上威士忌 每天都要新鲜
Black jack whiskey straight, every day changes your life
你就天生一副坏痞子样 对 就是你
You got that look that you know you're real bad, yeah baby you're right
你是大众情人 你是夜的主宰
Everybody loves you, baby you're the king of the night
我知道我已经抓住你所有的目光
And I'm the only one making sure I stay out of your sight
我会是你肆情的夜场 你迫不及待
You know I can make your night, you wanna get it
你真是我的菜 但这是一场错爱
You got something that I like but I might regret it
我和你我们是一场灾难
Me and you we're a disaster
而且你是我的危险头号人物
And you're only a danger to me
但是派对不能没有你
But the party ain't the same without ya
你是个万人迷大家都爱你
That's why you're so good for everybody else
不过碰上你 是我自找麻烦
But you're trouble for me
对 你就是我的麻烦人物
Yeah, you're trouble for me
甜言蜜语 挡不住你的激情挑逗
Sweet talk, here we go, tell me something credible
你让我好着迷 尤其是那种烟草和诱人的古龙水味道
You drive me crazy everytime I smell your cigarettes and cologne
我会是你肆情的夜场 你迫不及待
You know I can make your night, you wanna get it
你真是我的菜 但这是一场错爱
You got something that I like but I might regret it
敲敲你的高脚杯
Kiss kiss, tip your glass
你想要 我一定满足
I'll do whatever you ask for
想和我谈情说爱 先到舞池秀秀再说
But if you want my love You can only find it on the dancefloor
我会是你肆情的夜场 你迫不及待
You know I can make your night, you wanna get it
你真是我的菜 但这是一场错爱
You got something that I like but I might regret it
我和你我们是一场灾难
Me and you we're a disaster
但是派对不能没有你
But the party ain't the same without ya
你是个万人迷大家都爱你
That's why you're so good for everybody else
不过碰上你 是我自找麻烦
But you're trouble for me
对 你就是我的麻烦人物
Yeah, you're trouble for me
我会是你肆情的夜场 你迫不及待
You know I can make your night, you wanna get it
你真是我的菜 但这是一场错爱
You got something that I like but I might regret it
[I'm A Slave 4U]
我知道我还年轻
I know i may be young
但我也有情绪
but i’ve got feelings too
我想随心所欲做想做的事
And i need to do what i feel like doing
所以放我自由
So let me go
听我说
and just listen
你们总是把我当小女孩子
All you people look at me like i’m a little girl
从没想过我已准备好踏入成人的世界
Well did you ever think it be okay for me to step into this world
总是说小孩子不该去夜店
Always saying little girl don’t step into the club
我只是想知道什么 因为我好爱跳舞
Well i’m just trying to find out why cause dancing’s what i love
来吧来吧来吧来吧
Get it get it, get it get it (whoooa)
Get it get it, get it get it (whoooooa）
来吧来吧来吧来吧
Get it get it, get it get it (ooohhhh)
我是你爱情的奴隶
I’m a slave for you
I can not hold it，I can not control it
把持不住 控制不了
我是你爱情的奴隶
I’m a slave for you
I won’t deny it，I’m not trying to hide it
无法否认 不想隐藏
我知道看起来文静有点害羞
I know I may come off quiet I may come off shy
但当我看到帅哥 我就想讲话想跳舞
But I feel like talking,feel like dancing when I see this guy
什么实际什么逻辑 管他谁在乎
What's practical is logical what the hell who cares
我只知道你在这里跳舞我好开心
All I know is I'm so happy when you're dancing there
来吧来吧来吧来吧
Get it get it, get it get it (whoooa)
Get it get it, get it get it (whoooooa）
来吧来吧来吧来吧
Get it get it, get it get it (ooohhhh)
我是你爱情的奴隶
I’m a slave for you
I cannot hold it，I cannot control it
把持不住 控制不了
我是你爱情的奴隶
I’m a slave for you
I won’t deny it，I’m not trying to hide it
无法否认 不想隐藏
宝贝你不想贴近我跳舞吗
Baby don't you wanna dance upon me
找另一个时间另个地方
To another time and place
宝贝 你不想贴近我跳舞吗
Baby don't you wanna dance upon me
别管我叫什么名字什么年纪
Leaving behind my name my age
就这样
Like that
看着我
Now watch me
感觉不赖
Just feels good
我是你爱情的奴隶
I’m a slave for you
I cannot hold it，I cannot control it
把持不住 控制不了
我是你爱情的奴隶
I’m a slave for you
I won’t deny it，I’m not trying to hide it
无法否认 不想隐藏
就这样
Like that
现在看好我
Now watch me
好了多伦多 你们想更嗨么？
我不能听到你们哈
[I Wanna Go ]
最近我一直胡思乱想
Lately I've been stuck imagining
想放胆行动真实的想法
What I wanna do and what I really think
是时候爆发了
Time to blow out
是有点不恰当
Be a little inappropriate
因为我知道 每个人都在蠢蠢欲动
Cause I know that everybody's thinking it
当灯光一闪一闪
When the lights out
我好羞耻
Shame on me
想要释放我自己
To need release
肆无忌惮
Uncontrollably
我要完全释放 一路闪耀
I-I-I wanna go-o-o All the way-ay-ay
今晚大展迷情
Taking out my freak tonight
我要大胆表白 表露无遗
I-I-I wanna sho-o-ow All the dir-ir-irt
我早已神游欲海
I got running through my mind
我要完全释放 一路闪耀
I-I-I wanna go-o-o All the way-ay-ay
今晚大展迷情
Taking out my freak tonight
我要大胆表白 表露无遗
I-I-I wanna sho-o-ow All the dir-ir-irt
我早已神游欲海
I got running through my mind
众目睽睽让我神经紧绷
Lately, people got me all tied up
候场的倒计时让我一触即发
There's a countdown waiting for me to erupt
是时候爆发了
Time to blow out
总是对我处处使唤
I've been told who I should do it with
总是让我循规蹈矩乖一点
To keep both my hands above the blanket
当灯光一闪一闪
When the lights out
我好羞耻
Shame on me
想要释放我自己
To need release
肆无忌惮
Uncontrollably
我要完全释放 一路闪耀
I-I-I wanna go-o-o All the way-ay-ay
今晚大展迷情
Taking out my freak tonight
我要大胆表白 表露无遗
I-I-I wanna sho-o-ow All the dir-ir-irt
我早已神游欲海
I got running through my mind
我要完全释放 一路闪耀
I-I-I wanna go-o-o All the way-ay-ay
今晚大展迷情
Taking out my freak tonight
我要大胆表白 表露无遗
I-I-I wanna sho-o-ow All the dir-ir-irt
我早已神游欲海
I got running through my mind
我好羞耻
Shame on me
想要释放我自己
To need release
肆无忌惮
Uncontrollably
我要完全释放 一路闪耀
I-I-I wanna go-o-o All the way-ay-ay
今晚大展迷情
Taking out my freak tonight
我要完全释放 一路闪耀
I-I-I wanna sho-o-ow All the dir-ir-irt
我早已神游欲海
I got running through my mind
我要完全释放 一路闪耀
I-I-I wanna go-o-o All the way-ay-ay
今晚大展迷情
Taking out my freak tonight
我要大胆表白 表露无遗
I-I-I wanna sho-o-ow All the dir-ir-irt
我早已神游欲海
I got running through my mind
你们实在太棒了
都很不错
给他们一些掌声吧
喔！
我也爱你
好的
没事 我晚点打给你
好的 拜拜
你也高兴呀
⊙ω⊙   ＃￣▽￣＃
我爱你 多伦多
[Womanizer]
大明星
Superstar
你从哪里来 最近还好吗
Where you from, how's it going?
我了解你
I know you
看得出你又在玩什么把戏
Gotta clue whatcha doing
你在所有美眉面前装纯情
You can play brand new, to all the other chicks out there
但我知道你是什么人物
But I know what you are
你是什么人物 宝贝
What you are, baby
看看你
Look at you
续了不止一杯
Getting more than just a re-up
宝贝 你
Baby, you
玩偶身上有你操控的绳子
Got all the puppets with their strings up
装出一副好男人的样子
Faking like a good one
但我能看清事实
But I call'em when I see'em
我知道你是什么样的人物
I know what you are
你是什么人物 宝贝
What you are, baby
好色之徒
Womanizer
Woman-womanizer
你是好色之徒
You're a womanizer
喔 好色之徒
Oh, womanizer
喔 你是好色之徒 宝贝
Oh, you're a womanizer, baby
你 你 你是
You you you are
好色之徒好色之徒
Womanizer, womanizer
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
你让我心动
(You)You got me going
你充满魅力
(You)You're oh so charming
但你不过是一个
(You)But I can't do it
好色之徒
(You)You womanizer
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
你说我很疯狂
(You)You say I'm crazy
你为我疯狂
(You)I gotcha crazy
你不过是一个
(You)You're nothing but a
好色之徒
(You)Womanizer
大情圣
Lollipop
误判我会被你吸引
You must mistake me for a sucker
以为我
To think that I
会成为下个受害者
Would be a victim, not another
甜言蜜语随你怎么出击
Say you're playing how you want it
但我绝不落入你的陷阱
But no way I'm never gonna fall for you
永远不会 宝贝
Never you, baby
好色之徒
Womanizer
Woman-womanizer
你是好色之徒
You're a womanizer
喔 好色之徒
Oh, womanizer
喔 你是好色之徒 宝贝
Oh, you're a womanizer, baby
你 你 你是
You you you are
好色之徒好色之徒
Womanizer, womanizer
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
你让我心动
(You)You got me going
你充满魅力
(You)You're oh so charming
但你不过是一个
(You)But I can't do it
好色之徒
(You)You womanizer
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
你说我很疯狂
(You)You say I'm crazy
你为我疯狂
(You)I gotcha crazy
你不过是个
(You)You're nothing but a
好色之徒
(You)Womanizer
你为我疯狂
I got you crazy
好色之徒
Wowanizer
好色之徒好色之徒
Womanizer woman womanizer
你是一个好色之徒 喔 好色之徒 喔
You're a womanizer oh womanizer oh
你是一个好色之徒 宝贝
You're a womanizer baby
好色之徒 好色之徒
Womanizer woman womanizer
你是一个好色之徒 喔 好色之徒 喔
You're a womanizer oh womanizer oh
好色之徒
Wowanizer
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
你让我心动
(You)You got me going
你充满魅力
(You)You're oh so charming
但你不过是一个
(You)But I can't do it
好色之徒
(You)You womanizer
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
不要在那给我装假
Boy don't try to front
我知道你是什么人物
I know just what you are
你说我很疯狂
(You)You say I'm crazy
你为我疯狂
(You)I gotcha crazy
你只不过是个
(You)You're nothing but a
好色之徒
(You)Womanizer
好色之徒 好色之徒
Womanizer woman womanizer
你是一个好色之徒 喔 好色之徒 喔
You're a womanizer oh womanizer oh
你是一个好色之徒 宝贝
You're a womanizer baby
谢谢 多伦多 你们太棒了
谢谢
我本来是想统治世界的
时候到了
你在哪里 我的蛇蝎美人
你真是坏透了
我感觉到了
你很危险
今晚
我为你准备了一个惊喜
推她
你毁了我的梦想
今晚该结束了
今晚这场世纪之舞也该跳完了
就在这
此刻
把帐算清
你个小坏蛋
我抓到你了
[Toxic]
宝贝 难道你不知道 我殷殷的呼唤
baby, can't you see i'm calling
你这么俊俏 总叫我没有安全感
a guy like you should wear a warning
你真的太危险 我要坠入爱河
it's dangerous i'm falling
我无路可退 不想空等
there's no escape i can't wait
我需要你 让我拥有你
i need a hit baby, give me it
你是个危险情人 让我深深痴迷
you're dangerous i'm loving it
内心澎湃 无法平静
too high can't calm down
无法思考 情绪起伏不定
losing my head spinning round and round
你难道没有感应
do you feel me now?
你唇间的滋味 让我的心飘逸悬空
with the taste of your lips i'm on a ride
你是蛇蝎剧毒 我被你折服
your toxic tongue slipping mine
我尝到了天堂之毒
with the taste of the poison paradise
让我不能自拔
i'm addicted to you
你是蛇蝎剧毒
don't you know that your toxic?
我却为你深深着迷
and i love what you do
难道你不知道 你是蛇蝎剧毒
don't you know that your toxic?
现在要放弃你已经太迟
it's getting late to give you up
我已经啜饮恶魔的毒杯
i took a sip from a devil's cup
渐渐地 你的毒入侵我的身体
slowly, it's taking over me
内心澎湃 无法平静
too high can't calm down
飘飘欲仙 晕头转向
it's in the air and it's all around
你能感应到吗
can you feel me now?
你唇间的滋味 让我的心漂浮悬空
with the taste of your lips i'm on a ride
你是蛇蝎剧毒我被你折服
your toxic I'm slipping under
我尝到了天堂之毒
with the taste of the poison paradise
让我不能自拔
i'm addicted to you
难道你不知道 你是蛇蝎剧毒吗
don't you know that your toxic?
我却为你深深着迷
and i love what you do
难道你不知道 你是蛇蝎剧毒吗
don't you know that your toxic?
我却为你深深着迷
and i love what you do
让我不能自拔
i'm addicted to you
你唇间的滋味 让我的心漂浮悬空
with the taste of your lips i'm on a ride
你是蛇蝎剧毒 我被你折服
your toxic I'm slipping under
我尝到了天堂之毒
with the taste of the poison paradise
让我不能自拔
i'm addicted to you
难道你不知道 你是蛇蝎剧毒吗
don't you know that your toxic?
我却深深为你着迷
and i love what you do
难道你不知道 你是蛇蝎剧毒吗
don't you know that your toxic?
我却深深为你着迷
and i love what you do
难道你不知道 你是蛇蝎剧毒吗
don't you know that your toxic?
蛇蝎剧毒
toxic
[Till The World Ends]
我知道这只性感的猫咪已让你张口结舌
This kicked in got your tongs in knots I see
别害羞表白 我正有意与你为伴
Spit it out cuz im dying for company
知道你想入非非
I notice that you got it
知道我迫不及待
You notice that I want it
你知道我们可以进一步亲密 宝贝
You know that I can take it to the next level ba-by!
如果你想勾搭正妹
If you want this good shit
要比炮音更带劲
Sicker than the remix
宝贝 今晚我要嗨爆你的神经
Baby let me blow your mind tonight
我快受不了了 身体蠢蠢欲动
I can’t take it take it take no more
从没有像这样那么爽过
Never felt like felt like this before
把我带进舞池玩更刺激的
Come on get me get me off the floor
DJ你还等什么
DJ whatcha whatcha waitin' for!?
让视线停留在我的热舞节拍上
Watch me move when I loose when I lose it hard
忘情爱抚在昏天暗地的舞池中
Get you off with the touch dancing in the dark
注意我的打扮
You notice what I’m wearing
注意你的眼神
I notice that you are staring
你知道我们可以更进一步亲密 宝贝
You know that I can take it to the next level baby
比一线更辣 那就是我的猎物
Harder than the A-list Next one on my hit list
宝贝 今晚我要嗨爆你的神经
Baby let me blow your mind tonight!
我快受不了了 身体蠢蠢欲动
I can’t take it take it take no more
从没有像这样那么爽过
Never felt like felt like this before
把我带进舞池玩更刺激的
Come on get me get me off the floor
DJ你还等什么
DJ whatcha whatcha waiting for!?
见黎明将至
See the sunlight
也不要停止
We ain’t stopping
尽情舞动 直到天崩地裂
Keep on dancing till the world ends
如果你热血沸腾 释放吧
If you feel it let it happen
尽情舞动 直到世界末日
Keep on dancing till the world ends
猩猩好烦人 但我从容不迫
Chimpanzees is hating but I take it all in stride
丢一把香蕉放生回丛林里去
Put her in a jungle with bananas on the side
说能治好你 其实他说谎
Told you the revive your career but somebody lied
我说麻辣鸡不是这只炸鸡
I ain't talking poultry when I say this chicken's friiiiiiied
布兰妮 为什么跟你合作他们超眼红
Anyway Britney why they so jealous that you teamed up with me
他们都是小孩 妈妈来抱抱
Tell'em they my son yup yella mama pick me
那美女什么的回来？不知道，蛇蝎美人儿
Anyway burned bat ell,what's that,I don't know,Femme Fatale
瞧瞧 哭样 真是活该窝囊一辈子
Sniff sniff cries l done slayed your whole entire fucking life
喔喔 你搞来泄盐
OHOH you got some Epson Salt
我可以蹦上一天 你根本办不到
I done balled all day you ain't touched the court
什么 你累了 你要休息了
What what you tired you need a break
你太没趣了 瑞奇雷克
You was hot when Ricky Lake
见黎明将至
See the sunlight
也不要停下来
We ain't stopping
尽情舞动 直到天崩地裂
Keep on dancing till the world ends
如果你热血沸腾 释放吧
If you feel it let it happen
尽情舞动 直到天崩地裂
Keep on dancing till the world ends
如果你热血沸腾 释放吧
If you feel it let it happen
尽情舞动 直到天崩地裂
Keep on dancing till the world ends
谢谢 多伦多 你们真棒
Thanks Toronto you are amazing
谢谢
嘿嘿 观看满意么？
晚安各位 我爱你们
鸣谢 小燕子 韩宇森字幕男
再见！！！